the world?
Yeah. I don't think you can just hand
somebody something
without um
without some background without some
teaching something evolved out of
something. But if you can't just drop it
on somebody if they don't have a
background knowledge or they don't have
a chance to get educated about it or it
doesn't work in their lifestyle.
Yes.
So I think that that's like sometimes
that just doesn't work so well because
there's no um background for it or
there's no
context.
Yeah. the home maybe
doesn't have that same approach or
perspective
that the creators or the educators would
wish.
In a laboratory, we have a model that
works just well, but we move it into the
real world and we fail to see it
generalized. There isn't a respect for
its domain.
You need to know who the the receiving
party is. You need to really understand
Yes. who they are and what their
background is and meet them somewhere
closer
to what would work. Yes. What's